And I can also go to Visuals, so from the Visuals tab, I will be able to, again, generate
my images, stickers, icons, etc., or I can browse from all these images that it provides
me with, as well as shapes, for example, you know, whenever that you need shapes in your
project, whenever that you need, whatever, you know, organic shapes or sparkle illustrations,
you know, winter icons, sparkle photos, winter photos, you know, what else we have beach
photos, mountain photos, fruit icons, you know, all of these random stuff, we can also
search if we're looking for something special, so for example, I say, Christmas, right?
And I wait a little bit, it seems like I need to press enter, so I do that, yes, then
it starts searching for me, and as you see, all the visuals that are Christmas-related,
yeah, very beautiful.
All the visuals that are Christmas-related will be available for me, and by clicking on
each, I will be able to add that very visual into my design.